export const quizQuestions = [ 
    {
        question: "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
        options: ["Angular", "React", "Svelte", "Vue"],
        correctOptions: 1,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
        options: ["Var", "Let", "Const", "All of the above"],
        correctOptions: 3,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to call a function named myFunction?",
        options: ["call myFunction()", "execute myFunction()", "myFunction()", "run myFunction()"],
        correctOptions: 2,
        points: 20,
    },
    {
        question: "Which symbol is used for single-line comments is JavaScript?",
        options: ["//", "/* */", "<!-- -->", "#"],
        correctOptions: 0,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What does typeOf return when used with a string value?",
        options: ["Object", "Number", "String", "Undefined"],
        correctOptions: 2,
        points: 20,
    },
    {
        question: "How do you add a new element to an array in JavaScript?",
        options: ["arr.add()", "arr.push()", "arr.insert()", "arr.append"],
        correctOptions: 1,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to write an if statement in JavaScript?",
        options: ["if x > 5 then", "if (x > 5)", "if x > 5 {", "if x > 5:"],
        correctOptions: 1,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "How do you create an object in JavaScript?",
        options: ["let obj = {name: 'John', age: 30}", "let obj = (name: 'John', age: 30)", "let obj = [name: 'John', age: 30]", "let obj = 'name: John, age: 30'"],
        correctOptions: 0,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the result of 5 % 2",
        options: ["2.5", "1", "0", "5"],
        correctOptions: 1,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the value of x after executing let x = 10; x += 5;?",
        options: ["5", "10", "15", "undefined"],
        correctOptions: 2,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What does NaN stand for in JavaScript",
        options: ["Not a Null", "Not a Number", "No Assigned Number", "None Available Now"],
        correctOptions: 1,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "How do you round the number 4.7 to the nearest whole number in JavaScript?",
        options: ["Math.round(4.7)", "Math.ceil(4.7)", "Math.floor(4.7)", "round(4.7)"],
        correctOptions: 0,
        points: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default value of an uninitialized variable in JavaScript?",
        options: ["null", "0", "undefined", "false"],
        correctOptions: 2,
        points: 20,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a way to declare an arrow function in JavaScript?",
        options: ["let myFunction = () => {}", "let myFunction = function() {}", "function myFunction() {}","myFunction => ()"],
        correctOptions: 0,
        points: 20,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is a JavaScript keyword used to loop through arrays?",
        options: ["for", "each", "loop", "while"],
        correctOptions: 0,
        points: 20,
    },
]